http://www.logbookpro.com/privacy.aspx

My Account|
Login
Advanced Search
Privacy Policy
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.
By accessing or otherwise using this web site, or any of NC Software's web sites, you agree to be bound
contractually by this Privacy Policy.
Effective Date: May 25, 2018
NC Software, Inc. ("NC Software") is committed to maintaining your confidence as to how we use your information. This privacy policy applies to the services (“Services”) available at the websites (the “Sites”) owned and operated by NC Software, including the site maintained at nc-software.com. This Privacy Policy explains when and how NC Software collects and uses personal information. Unless we say otherwise, the use of information collected through NC Software’s Services and Sites shall be limited to the purpose of providing the Services and Sites. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Services, Sites or any of NC Software’s business services or products.
You should look also at any license agreement you may have with NC Software and any other terms of use that may apply. To be clear, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party applications that integrate with the Services, any third-party products, services or businesses or any websites controlled by any third-parties.
Before you read further, your use of the Sites and Services (and any dispute over privacy) is subject to this Privacy Policy, which may be changed from time to time. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy, or any changes to it, you should stop using the Services and Sites.
If you have any questions about NC Software's privacy practices or its handling of information, please contact:
NC Software, Inc. Attn: Privacy Policy PMB 5115 1st Floor 2801 Centerville RdWilmington, DE 19808-1609 Email: legal@nc-software.com
What We Collect
NC Software collects and receives information based upon your use of the Services and the Sites. The information may be collected in a number of ways.
For example, NC Software may ask you to provide personal data such as a name, email address, physical address, phone number and, if you are making a purchase, billing information (which may also be collected by NC Software's payment processors).
NC Software may also gather information about, and monitor, your use of the Sites and Services and may work with third-parties to assist us in doing so. To be clear, certain anonymous information may be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies. While the names, means and methods may change, passive collection tools may include cookies, tags and navigational data.
For example, with a "cookie," a website sends a text file to your browser. The information generated by the cookie about your use of a website (which can include your Internet protocol (IP) address, clickstream data, and connection information) will be stored. While many browsers automatically accept cookies, you should be able to modify your browser to decline cookies if you prefer; however, certain website features might not work without cookies. NC Software uses temporary "session" cookies in order for you to view content and browse the Sites. "Persistent" cookies may be used to help you navigate the Sites more efficiently.
How We Use Information
NC Software may use passively collected information, which can help us to provide better service, customize the Sites and Services based on your preferences, including providing selective advertising, compile and analyze statistics and trends, and otherwise administer and improve the Sites. We may share anonymous, passive information with third parties, but only in an aggregated form. In other words, the information would not be tied directly to you.
NC Software uses the information in providing the Services and Sites and for its legitimate business interests. The use of the information can include administration of the Sites and Services, technical support, security, communicating with you, including about promotional offers and information related to the Services and Sites, and, of course, improving our offerings.
Please note that NC Software may use third-parties to assist it in providing the Services and Sites. Where we do so, the third-parties may have access to personal information, but only in connection the service we have asked them to perform as with, for example, processing credit card payments or hosting sites containing personal information. They are not to use the information for any unapproved purpose.
In the event that NC Software is acquired by, or merges with, a third party, or if we sell all or a portion of our property, such as the Sites or Services, we reserve the right to transfer information as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.
Additional Information
While it may be obvious, if the Sites or Services contain links to websites controlled by third-parties, NC Software is not responsible for those sites or any actions taken by those third-parties, including how they may use information they collect about you.
Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, NC Software will release information when it believes disclosing it is reasonably necessary (1) to comply with applicable laws, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, or (2) to investigate or enforce violations of our rights or protect the rights, property or safety of NC Software and, importantly, its customers.
If you need help, we can assist you with reasonable requests in managing information over which we have control. To the extent it applies to it, NC Software is committed to complying with the General Data Protection Regulation when dealing with personal information from the European Union, the European Economic Area and their member states, Switzerland and the United Kingdom. You may have certain rights in relation to the information, which may include the ability to request access to information, and also to delete or correct information.
Material Modifications since May 25, 2018: none
Home|
Privacy|
Terms|
Policies|
Versions|
Mailing Lists|
Support|
Subscribe to our Newsletter:
© 2020 NC Software, Inc. All rights reserved.
Logbook Pro® is a registered trademark of NC Software, Inc.
All other trademarks or registered trademarks are property of their respective owners
